let Questions = [
    {
        "Question": "What does the term 'Full Stack Development' refer to?",
        "Options": [
            "Development that involves stack data structures",
            "Development that involves front-end and back-end programming",
            "Development that involves only backend programming",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "Answer": "Development that involves front-end and back-end programming"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is not a front-end technology?",
        "Options": [
            "HTML",
            "CSS",
            "JavaScript",
            "SQL"
        ],
        "Answer": "SQL"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The purpose of the Front-end framework in Full stack development is ____.",
        "Options": [
            "To provide the client-side interface",
            "To manage database",
            "To reduce the server load",
            "To send http requests"
        ],
        "Answer": "To provide the client-side interface"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Amongst which of the following programming language is used as a server-side language?",
        "Options": [
            "Python",
            "C++",
            "JavaScript",
            "Both A and C"
        ],
        "Answer": "Both A and C"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Database in Full stack development is used to ____.",
        "Options": [
            "Styling HTML pages",
            "Storing and retrieving data",
            "Handling errors on server-side",
            "Rendering web pages"
        ],
        "Answer": "Storing and retrieving data"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is Git?",
        "Options": [
            "Framework",
            "Version control system",
            "Database",
            "Package manager"
        ],
        "Answer": "Version control system"
    },
    {
        "Question": "CRUD stands for ____.",
        "Options": [
            "Create, Read, Upload, Delete",
            "Create, Read, Upgrade, Deploy",
            "Create, Remove, Upgrade, Delete",
            "Create, Read, Update, Delete"
        ],
        "Answer": "Create, Read, Update, Delete"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The term 'deployment' refers to",
        "Options": [
            "Running the project on a server to make it accessible to all",
            "Bundling all the project files into a single file",
            "Removing unnecessary files",
            "Updating existing project"
        ],
        "Answer": "Running the project on a server to make it accessible to all"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Is JavaScript synchronous or asynchronous?",
        "Options": [
            "Synchronous",
            "Asynchronous",
            "Both",
            "Synchronous but can be used as asynchronous"
        ],
        "Answer": "Synchronous but can be used as asynchronous"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Amongst which of the following is a back-end framework in Python?",
        "Options": [
            "Django",
            "Flask",
            "Both A and B",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "Answer": "Both A and B"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Amongst which of the following type of database is used in Full stack development?",
        "Options": [
            "Relational",
            "JSON",
            "XML",
            "GraphQL"
        ],
        "Answer": "Relational"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The role of view in model-view-controller architecture is ____.",
        "Options": [
            "Displaying data to the user",
            "Optimize database queries",
            "Handle client's request",
            "Manage server-side routing"
        ],
        "Answer": "Displaying data to the user"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Amongst which of the following is not a NoSQL database used in Full Stack Development?",
        "Options": [
            "MongoDB",
            "PostgreSQL",
            "CouchDB",
            "Hadoop"
        ],
        "Answer": "Hadoop"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In HTML, the <iframe> tag is used to ____.",
        "Options": [
            "Embed another HTML document or a web page within the current document",
            "Insert a video in the HTML document",
            "Create a frame in an HTML document",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "Answer": "Embed another HTML document or a web page within the current document"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In an HTML document, which tag is used to add JavaScript code?",
        "Options": [
            "<javascript>",
            "<js>",
            "<script>",
            "<java>"
        ],
        "Answer": "<script>"
    }
    
]

export default Questions;